Tremble, right hand of mine...
（岡部倫太郎(おかべりんたろう)）震えよ 我が右腕
By the contract we made, I order you
契約に基づき 命じる
to shroud yourself in black flame and grant my desire!
漆黒の炎をまといて
我が望みを満たせ
はあっ！
（椎名(しいな)まゆり）あーっ
Now I can't heat up my fried chicken!
これじゃ から揚げ 温められないよ
You sure about this?
（牧瀬紅莉栖(まきせくりす)）いいんですか？
Mayuri, this is no longer a microwave.
If you join the lab, you'll be dealing with this all day.
ラボメンになると
ああいうのに つきあわされますよ
It's a time machine!
That's not fair!
横暴だよ
じゃあ オカリン
新しく電子レンジ 買ってきてよ
Then go buy me a new microwave, Okarin.
フフン そんな金(かね)はない
I don't have the money.
（岡部）うっ！
I told you photographing me is prohibited.
俺を写すのは禁止だと言ったはずだ
（桐生萌郁(きりゅうもえか)）記念に…
（紅莉栖）え？
It's to celebrate.
No photos!
（岡部）とにかく撮るな！
（萌郁）ん…
Okay, done programming.
（橋田 至(はしだいたる)）
よーし プログラム 終わった
電話レンジ セカンドエディション
バージョン1,03 完成！
Phone Microwave, 2nd edition, Version 1.03 is done.
これで電話レンジの携帯から
好きな番号に―
Now you can use the Phone Microwave's cell phone
Ｄメールを転送できるぜい
to send a D-mail to any phone you like!
You did it, Daru!
でかしたぞ ダル！
Then let's continue our experiments.
それじゃあ 実験再開ね
Is it really a time machine?
本当に… タイムマシン？
Don't tell anyone, okay?
絶対に口外するなよ
（まゆり）ぷはー
（岡部）うん？
But don't you think the landlord will get mad at us?
でも店長さんに
また怒られないかなあ
うっ…
（阿万音鈴羽(あまねすずは)）あ？
Part-time warrior!
（岡部）バイト戦士！
おーい！
（まゆり･天王寺 綯(てんのうじなえ)）
トゥットゥルー
Mayuri, be quiet!
（岡部）まゆり 静かに！ あっ…
Where's Mr. Braun?
（岡部）ミスターブラウンは？
（鈴羽）誰？
Who's that?
Don't call my dad Mr. Braun...
（綯）
お父さんは“ミスターブラウン”
なんかじゃ…
ああ 店長なら出張サービス中
You mean the boss? He's out on a service call.
I don't think he'll be back for a while.
しばらく
帰ってこないんじゃないかな？
Seriously?!
（岡部）本当か！
（鈴羽）でなきゃここでサボって…
If it weren't, I wouldn't be screwing around outside
Mayuri.
（岡部）まゆり…
（まゆり）うん
Okay.
Tutturu
Received Mail
From: Mayuri
Subject: (None)
--   Mayushii
（一同）おおっ！
This is...
（萌郁）これは…
うわ 光った…
I saw a light.
～
Divergence
Singularity
（まゆり）あーあ…
Juicy Fried Chicken Number 1 would taste better...
「ジューシーから揚げ№１(ワン)」の
ほうが おいしいんだけどな
あっ
Hey, there's no Dr Pepper!
おい ドクぺがないではないか！
They were out.
売り切れてたの
If they're out, keep looking until you find some!
（岡部）売り切れていたのなら
見つけるまで探す！
That's what it means to be a Dr Pepperian.
それが ドクトルペッパリアン
というものではないか！
They didn't have any.
（紅莉栖）
なかったものは なかったんだから
しかたないでしょ
What do you want me to do about it?
いらないの？
You want some or not?
うぐっ…
Geez...
まったく…
What kind of mad scientist worries about not getting enough vegetables?
野菜不足を気にしてる
マッドサイエンティストが―
どこの世界にいるというのだ
Let's begin the Round Table.
では円卓会議を始める
It's hot in here. Let's open a window.
（橋田）つうか 窓 開けよ
暑いっしょ？
What are you doing, Daru?
（岡部）何をしているのだ ダル！
What if the Organization discovers our secret...
機関に我々の秘密を
知られたらどうする！
Delusion fail!
（橋田）妄想 乙(おつ)！
（岡部）んっ？ うん？
What's a Round Table?
（岡部）フン！
We will now move Operation Urd to stage two,
これよりオペレーションウルドを
第２段階に進め―
（岡部）Ｄメールを―
and take experiments on D-mail to a more practical level.
より実践的に使う実験を
行おうと思う
（まゆり）夏は麦茶だよね
In the summer, you gotta have barley tea.
萌郁さんも飲む？
Want some too, Moeka?
“実践的”って 何するんだお？
Practical? What are we going to do?
Change the past.
過去を変える
Wait... That's too dangerous.
待って！
そんなの危険すぎる
If you create a time paradox...
もしもタイムパラドックスが
起こったら…
Assistant, as a scientist,
助手よ
お前は科学者として―
aren't you interested in whether we can alter the past using D-mail?
Ｄメールを使い
過去を変えられるかどうか―
確かめたくはないのか？
W-Well...
（紅莉栖）そっ それは…
（まゆり）でも 何を変えるの？
But what will we change?
Good question.
いい質問だ
Here's what I want to accomplish with this operation...
俺が本作戦において
成し遂げたいこと それは―
Win the lottery.
宝くじを当てることだ
Okarin... Mayushii is very sad.
（まゆり）オカリン…
まゆしぃは悲しいです
I'm in.
（橋田）僕は賛成
If I had money, I could buy new parts for the computer,
カネがあればＰＣパーツ買えるし
「メイクイーン」にも行き放題…
and I could go to May Queen all I want.
Don't you think we should work toward world peace?
（まゆり）もっとね…
世界が平和になる方法とか
考えるべきじゃないかな
Like give everyone in the world an Upa cushion...
例えば世界中の人たちが
うーぱクッションを…
Okabe, that's really lame.
（紅莉栖）岡部… 志 低すぎ
It's an experiment to see if we can change the past.
過去を変えられるかどうかの
実験なのだ
一番 分かりやすいではないか
That would be the easiest way to tell!
But basically, you just want money, right?
でも目的は お金でしょ？
Shut up, Celeb 17!
（岡部）黙れ
セレブ セブンティーン！
セッ セレ… はあ？
Cele... Huh?
Celeb 17!
セレブ セブンティーン
I don't want to hear anything from a woman
親のカネでホテル住まいを
しているような人間に―
living in a hotel on her parent's money!
とやかく言われる筋合いはない
I'm 18.
私はエイティーンだ
But there are all kinds of lottery tickets.
（橋田）つうかさあ…
宝くじにも いろいろあるっしょ？
Which one do you want?
どれにするん？
Well...
うむ それは…
うん？
What's wrong?
（まゆり）どーしたの？
No...
あっ いや…
Where'd Moeka go?
萌郁はどこに行った？
（紅莉栖）あれ？
（岡部）ハッ！
Huh?
（萌郁）うん…
Wait!
待てーい！
（橋田）よいしょ
Sheesh... I can't take my eyes off you for a second.
まったく油断も隙もない
返事 なかったから…
It's because you didn't respond.
I really want to borrow
the IBN 5100. Please...
Ill take that as a yes?
（岡部）くっ…
Is she supposed to be a valley girl LOL?
これはもしや
“スイーツ（笑）(かっこわらい)”ってやつ？
Christina, keep a close eye on her,
（岡部）クリスティーナ！
勝手に動き回らないように―
so she doesn't wander around!
しっかり見張っているのだぞ
How am I supposed to do that?
（紅莉栖）
“見張ってろ”って言われても…
Do you want to see the lab, Moeka?
（まゆり）萌郁さん
ラボ 見たいの？
I'll show you around later.
じゃあ あとで案内したげるね
Mayushii is good at that!
まゆしぃ 得意なんだよ
紅莉栖ちゃんにも してあげたんだ
I did it for Kurisu too!
（萌郁）ん…
Where should I start?
（まゆり）
まずは どこから見せようかな…
Oh, I see.
（橋田）なるへそ　ロト６(シックス)ね
The Lotto 6.
Every Thursday, the winning numbers are announced.
毎週木曜日に
当選番号が発表されている
We'll send the numbers to the past.
そいつを過去に送るのだ
We're really doing this?
本当にやるの？
You have any other bright ideas?
（岡部）
ほかにいい代案があるのか？
Which division numbers do you want?
当選番号だけど どれにする？
By the way, first division prize is...
ちなみに１等は…
ちょっ… ２億とか！
two hundred million yen!
えっ？
Two hundred million yen?
に… ２億！
Wait, Daru.
待て ダル！
Two hundred million yen is a bit much.
（岡部）２億は ちょっと…
（橋田）え？
い… １等は さすがに目立ちすぎる
First division would draw too much attention.
お… 俺は
機関に追われてる身だからな
The Organization is chasing me, after all.
You have cold feet, don't you?
ビビったな
に… ２等は？
What's second division?
（橋田）えっと… ２千３百万円
Twenty-three million yen.
Third?
３等！
Seven hundred thousand.
（橋田）70万
（岡部）そっ それ！
We'll go with that!
Okabe's a chicken, isn't he?
（紅莉栖）岡部って結構チキンね
（岡部）
それがタイムパラドックスを…
That's coming from someone worried about a time paradox, Celeb 17?
And this is the Upa cushion!
（まゆり）…で
これが うーぱクッション
When you're tired or feeling down,
疲れたときとか元気がないときに
ムギューってするの
you give it a hug, like this!
（萌郁）ん…
And this is the fridge!
（まゆり）でね こっちが冷蔵庫
（まゆり）今日の中身は…
What's inside today?
Um...
（萌郁）あの…
（まゆり）うん？
（岡部）おーい！
シャイニング･フィンガー
Hey!
Shining Finger!
（萌郁）ん？
Here's your first mission as a lab member.
（岡部）お前にラボメンとしての
最初の任務を与える
（萌郁）え…
（まゆり）おお 初仕事だね
Ooh, your first job!
Think of what to write in the D-mail.
Ｄメールの文面を考えるのだ
Something that'll make the me of one week ago want to buy a Lotto 6 ticket.
何も知らない １週間前の俺に―
ロト６を買おうと思わせる
文章をな
Seven days ago would be 168 hours, so about 170 seconds on the timer should do it?
（紅莉栖）７日前だから…
168時間 170秒ってところかしら
（岡部）フム…
Buy Lotto-6
You'll win!
Sounds about right.
こんなもんだろう
Okay, we're ready.
（紅莉栖）じゃあ 準備完了ね
（岡部）
フフン ついにシュタインズ･
ゲートを開く時が来たな
At last, the time has come to open Steins Gate!
That again?
またそれ？ ホント飽きないわね
You really never tire of it, do you?
And you need to stop whining about it every time.
お前こそ いちいち水を差すな
（岡部）あ？
You looked like you were having fun.
楽しそう… だったから
（岡部）はあ？
（紅莉栖）別に楽しくなんか！
I-It's not like I'm having fun, all right?
That said, our assistant sure is a tsundere.
（橋田）それにしても この助手
ツンデレであーる
Who's a tsundere?!
誰がツンデレだ！
Ooh, Miss Makise, you know what a tsundere is?
ほお 牧瀬氏
ツンデレの意味が分かるん？
えっ？ し… 知らないわよ！
I don't!
No, you definitely responded like you did.
（岡部）いや
確かに知ってる反応だったな
I said I haven't!
（紅莉栖）
知らないったら 知らないってば！
Okay, I'm starting up the microwave.
んじゃ レンジ 起動させるぜよ
That's too dangerous.
（紅莉栖）
そんなの 危険すぎる
If you create a time paradox...
もしもタイムパラドックスが
起こったら…
ハッ ううっ…
Why am I so scared?
（岡部）
いや 何を弱気になってんだ…
El Psy Congroo!
エル･プサイ…
コングルゥ！
Sending...
Sent
うっ ううう…
（まゆり）オカリーン
Okarin!
オーカリーン！
オカリン？
（岡部）ハッ…
Are you okay?
（まゆり）大丈夫？
い… 今のは？
Wh-What was that?
ハッ！
あ…
How long have I been standing here?
俺は何分ぐらい ここに立ってた？
About 30 seconds, I guess.
（まゆり）ええ？
んー 30秒くらいかな…
30秒？
Thirty seconds?
You don't remember?
覚えてないの？
We were just talking about an experiment to see if we could change the past with a D-mail.
さっきまでＤメールで過去を変える
実験の話をしてたじゃない
そしたら…
Then...
You ran over to the Phone Microwave
急に電話レンジちゃんの
所に来て―
and started panting.
ハア ハアって
言いだして…
Mayushii, can you say "panting" again?
（橋田）まゆ氏
今の“ハア ハア”ってとこ…
Stop it, pervert!
（紅莉栖）やめなさい 変態！
（橋田）はい
（一同）あっ…
あ… ハッ！
Buy Lotto-6
届いてる…
It's here.
You'll win!
Okabe, are you really all right?
（紅莉栖）岡部 ホントに大丈夫？
（岡部）カネは？
（紅莉栖）ヒッ！
Where's the money?
ロト６だ！
The Lotto 6!
Cel. Seven, did I win third prize?
セレセブ 俺は３等を当てたのか？
Don't call me Cel. Seven....
セレセブ 言うな！
What are you talking about?
…って 何の話よ？
なっ 何ってお前…
What do you mean? You...
Okarin?
（まゆり）オカリン？
（萌郁）ん…
The experiment?
実験だ！
We did an experiment to see if we could change the past with the D-mail...
俺たちはＤメールを使って
過去を変える実験を…
We were just talking about what we could
だから今
どんな内容のメールがいいか―
do for the experiment.
みんなで話してたんじゃない
（岡部）ええっ？
Mayushii wants something that'll bring about world peace!
まゆしぃは世界が平和になる
方法とか いいな
世界中の…
Like giving everyone in the world an Upa cushion!
本当に覚えてないのか？
You really don't remember...
（紅莉栖･まゆり）あ…
Come in!
（まゆり）どうぞ
It's Ruka!
（まゆり）
あっ るか君　いらっしゃい
Welcome!
（漆原(うるしばら)るか）あ…
凶真(きょうま)さん すみませんでした！
Kyouma, I'm sorry!
（まゆり）るか君？
Ruka?
This...
（るか）これ…
（岡部）ハッ
02, 12, 18...
０ ２ １ ２ １ ８…
同じだ
It's the same.
Rukako! Where did you get this?
るか子 お前 これをどこで？
えっ？ あの…
Um... You gave me the numbers.
僕 凶真さんに
数字を教えてもらって…
I did?
俺が？
You told me to buy it since it might win.
“当たるかもしれない数字だから
買ってみろ”って…
Wh-When?
へっ… いつ？
One week ago.
１週間前です
Wow, Okarin's a psychic!
わあ！
オカリンは予知能力者だね
…で るか氏
ロト６ 当てたん？
So, Ruka, did you win?
それが…
Well... I got one of the numbers wrong.
番号を１つ 間違えてしまって…
えっ？ ハッ…
So close!
（橋田）うおっ 惜しい！
Too close!
惜しすぎる！
Okabe, did you use the Phone Microwave to...
岡部… あんた まさか
電話レンジで？
あっ…
Hey, there's no Dr Pepper!
（岡部）
ドクぺがないではないか！
They didn't have any.
（紅莉栖）
なかったものは なかったんだから
しかたないでしょ
What do you want me to do about it?
There's no doubt that I sent the D-mail,
（岡部）
俺は確かにＤメールを送ったはずだ
but there's no record of it.
しかし 送信履歴がない
The past has been changed?
過去が書き換えられた
ということか？
They didn't remember the experiment,
あいつらは実験のことを
覚えていなかった
一緒に話し合い
一緒に見ていたはずなのに
even though we all talked about it, and we all observed.
Only I remember.
俺だけが覚えている
Only I...
俺だけが…
This feeling! It's just like back then...
この感覚 あのときと一緒だ
What's going on?
どういうことなんだ？
What's that?
（綯）それ なあに？
大切なもの
Something important.
（鈴羽）あっ…
（綯）ううっ…
What's wrong?
どうした？
あ…
You look like you've been brainwashed.
（鈴羽）洗脳されたような顔してる
Brainwashed...
洗脳…
It's possible.
そうかもしれない
But was I the one brainwashed... or were they?
洗脳されたのは 俺のほうか―
あいつらのほう…
What?
なんだ？ うっ…
うっ…
（鈴羽）くっ
ハア… チップは入ってない
There's no chip.
（岡部）え…
It's okay.
（鈴羽）大丈夫 洗脳されていない
You're not brainwashed.
チ… チップ？
Chip?
What's "brainwashed"?
“洗脳”って何？
（鈴羽）それは…
That's...
I, Hououin Kyouma, will tell you.
それは この鳳凰院(ほうおういん)凶真が―
教えてやろう
（綯）う…
I guess Nae's scared of Okabe Rintarou.
綯は岡部倫太郎が怖いみたいだね
There's something I want to ask you.
聞きたいことがある
うん？
Electricity?
（鈴羽）放電？
グラグラ揺れるヤツ？
You mean when there are all those sparks?
You did it before, didn't you?
さっき１回 あったよね？
There should've been one 10 minutes ago.
（岡部）
10分くらい前にも あったはずだ
I didn't notice that one.
（鈴羽）そっちは気付かなかったな
What about you, Nae?
（鈴羽）綯は？
（綯）ううん
Nope!
（岡部）フム…
You really are a pervert!
（紅莉栖）
あんたってホント変態ね！
I'm not a pervert!
（橋田）僕は変態じゃないよ！
I'm a pervert-gentleman!
変態紳士だよ！
See?
ねっ？
聞こえてくるって言ったでしょ？
I told you that you can hear it.
I didn't know it was this bad...
これほどまでとは…
ハッ！
Did you hear about the time machine?
もしかして お前
タイムマシンの話も…
Yeah. Nice job, I guess!
うん やるねえ この！
Let me warn you...
忠告するが…
I know... I won't tell anyone.
分かってるって
誰にも言わないから
Are you worried about something related to the time machine?
あっ ひょっとして―
タイムマシンのことで
悩んでるとか？
Then why not ask John Titor?
だったらさ
ジョン･タイターに聞いてみたら？
ハッ！
Come to think of it, John Titor mentioned this.
（岡部）
そういえば タイターは言っていた
If you go to the past and change it,
“過去へ行き
そこで過去を変えると―”
this alters something called the divergence number,
“ダイバージェンスと呼ばれる
数値が変動し―”
“世界は別の世界線に移動する”
and the world line moves to another world.
“その移動のとき―”
When there's a world line shift, people's memories are altered,
“変化が生じる以前の
世界線での記憶は消去され”
and memories of the new world are created.
“新たな世界線での記憶が
再構築される”と
The D-mail moved the world line
Ｄメールにより―
from a world where Rukako didn't buy the Lotto 6 ticket
るか子がロト６を
買わなかった世界線から―
to one where he did.
買った世界線へと移動した
The world line changed, and so did the past.
世界線が変わり
過去の流れも変わったのだ
In this world,
ここはロト６を当てるための
Ｄメールを―
I didn't send the D-mail with the winning Lotto 6 number
過去に送らなかった世界
into the past.
It's not that the other lab members don't remember the experiment.
まゆりたちは
覚えていないのではない
実験そのものが
なかった世界なのだ
It never happened.
So why am I the only one who remembers?
では なぜ俺にだけ
その記憶があるんだ？
（クラクション）
（鈴羽）あ…
Oh, no!
ヤバッ！
Nae, whatever he asks, don't tell him I was slacking off!
綯 何 聞かれても―
私がサボってたって
言っちゃダメだよ
Will you give me a ride on your bike?
（綯）
今度は自転車 乗せてくれる？
I will!
（鈴羽）乗せる 乗せる
（鈴羽）岡部倫太郎
（岡部）えっ？
Okabe Rintarou!
I'm on your side, okay?
応援してるからね
（岡部）あ… ああ
（天王寺裕吾(ゆうご)）
フフ フフフン…
うん？
…にゃろう
You!
（綯）お父さん
Daddy!
（天王寺）岡部！
Okabe!
俺の娘に何をしていた！
What were you doing with my daughter?!
はあ？　まっ 待ってくれ
俺は何も…
W-Wait! I wasn't doing anything!
Shut up!
うるせえ！
A guy like you wouldn't be able to control his desires if left alone with my adorable daughter!
俺のカワイイ娘と二人っきりで―
お前(めえ)みてえな野郎が
欲望 抑えきれるわけがねえだろ
Do you always think about me like that?
どういう目で人のことを…
第一 二人きりでいたわけではない
And we weren't alone...
今の今まで
鈴羽もここにいたのだ！
Suzuha was just here too.
What? Is that true, Nae?
なに！
本当か 綯？
I promised, so I can't say she was slacking off.
約束だから サボってたって
言っちゃダメなの
What?
（天王寺）なに！
オラッ バイト！
Hey! Part-timer!
くわばら くわばら…
Knock on wood!
You were slacking off!
（天王寺）
てめえ サボってやがったな！
Argh, you left the 42-inch on!
だあっ！
42型もつけっぱなしじゃねえか
I-I'm sorry!
（鈴羽）ごっ ごめんなさーい！
I'll explain why later.
（岡部）事情はあとで話す
We're stopping the experiment for today.
今日の実験は中止だ
みんな 解散してくれ
Everyone, please go home.
（一同）えっ？
Okarin...
オカリン…
So, little miss assistant there, you're not going home?
（岡部）…で そこの助手
お前は帰らないのか？
I'm just thinking about something.
ちょっと考え事
（岡部）フン そうか
I see.
ホテルに帰っても
独りぽっちでさみしいから―
You'd be all alone if you went back to the hotel,
so you want me to spend time with you.
この俺に かまってほしい
というわけだな
Right, little Cel. Seven.?
お子様セレセブめ
（紅莉栖）
だから セレセブって言うな
Don't call me Cel. Seven.!
I've gotta send this text message.
俺はメールをする用事があるのだ
どうしても
ここにいたいのならば―
If you want to stay here, be quiet, The Zombie.
邪魔をせず静かにしているのだな
ザ･ゾンビ
その呼び方が一番カチンとくる
That's the name that bugs me the most.
（ため息）
You're like a girl, waiting for a message from her crush.
（紅莉栖）恋する乙女が―
好きな相手からのメールを
待ってるみたい
You really want attention that much?
（岡部）
そんなに かまってほしいのか？
えっ…
メールの相手 誰なの？
Who was that message for?
John Titor.
（岡部）ジョン･タイターだ
えっ？
（岡部）ハッ
Rukako
The Lottery
I'm really sorry
ああ…
（岡部）うん？
From: Shining Finger
Subject: I Had Fun
Next time, tell me about the time machine.
It's a promise. A promise, right?
Bye! Moeka
くっ！ このっ このっ…
（紅莉栖のため息）
（ため息）
（岡部）うん？
Daru
ダル？
Daru?
もしもし？
Hello.
Okarin, I realized I made a huge mistake!
（橋田）あっ オカリン？
実はさ…
とんでもないミスに気付いたんだ！
ミス？ なんだ？
A mistake? What?
Actually... Actually...
（橋田）実は…
実はさ…
I left my wallet at the lab!
（橋田）ラボに財布 忘れてきたお
（岡部）なに？
What?
So now I can't get into May Queen!
（橋田）おかげで
「メイクイーン」に入れないお
Okarin, would you...
（橋田）オカリン 悪いけど…
（岡部）くっ！
（岡部）フンッ！
（まゆり）
トゥットゥルー　オカリン？
Okarin!
なんだ まゆりか
Oh, it's you Mayuri.
あっ
Daru's with you, right?
ダルも一緒にいるのだろう？
You don't need to lend him money, okay?
カネを貸す必要はないからな
（まゆり）うん 分かった
Got it.
So, Okarin, do you feel better?
（まゆり）でね オカリン
元気になった？
If you don't, you can hug Mayushii's Upa, okay?
まだだったら―
まゆしぃのうーぱを
ムギューってしても いいからね
そしたら元気出るから
Then you'll feel better.
Okay.
ああ… もう切るぞ
バイト 頑張れよ
I'm hanging up.
Good luck at work.
（まゆり）
うん ありがとう　じゃあね
Thanks.
Bye!
Okabe, you're smiling.
（紅莉栖）岡部 にやけてる
んっ むっ…
おおっ
It's here!
（岡部）来たっ！
（紅莉栖）ハッ…
I read your message.
（タイター）
“メールを読みました”
Just as you deduced,
“あなたの推測どおり
過去を変え―”
the past was changed, and the world line has undoubtedly moved.
“世界線が移動したことに
間違いないでしょう”
The one thing I don't understand
“唯一 分からないことは―”
“あなたに過去改変前の記憶が
存在しているということです”
is why you retain your memories from before the change.
Is that true?
“それは事実ですか？”
It's true.
（岡部）事実です
以前にも
同じようなことがありました
Something similar happened before.
どういうことでしょう？
What does this mean?
I don't know.
（タイター）“分かりません”
“メールによる過去改変など―”
The concept of changing the past
via email was never considered,
“私がいた2036年においても
想定されていなかった事象です”
even in the year 2036.
You changed the past and moved world lines.
“あなたは今回 過去を改変し
世界線を移動させました”
But it's never been confirmed if
“しかし世界線を越えて
記憶を維持し―”
anyone alive can maintain their memories
“その変動を
観測できる人間など―”
over a world line jump and observe the change.
“今までに確認されたことは
ありません”
But...
“ですが… キョーマ”
Kyouma, you may have that power.
“あなたにはその力が
あるのかもしれません”
You may be able to lead the world
“あなたならば 世界を導くことが
できるかもしれません”
beyond Divergence 1%...
“ダイバージェンス１％の
向こう側へ…”
Lead the world?
“世界を導く”だと？
くっ…
（岡部）“ダイバージェンス
１％の向こう側”とは？
What lies beyond Divergence 1%?
そこに いったい
何があるというのですか？
What happens then?
Sending...
Sent
（岡部）くっ…
What lies beyond it is true freedom.
（タイター）
“その先にあるのは真の自由です”
“その壁を越えなければ
未来はディストピアとなる”
If you can't cross that barrier,
the future will become a dystopia.
（岡部）ハッ あ…
My goal is to change the future.
（タイター）
“私の目的は未来を変えること”
“そして その力を持っているのは
あなたかもしれない”
And you may be the one who has that power.
（岡部）うっ！
（紅莉栖）
あっ… 岡部 どうしたの？
Okabe, what's wrong?
What's he talking about?
（岡部）
何を言ってるんだ こいつは…
Me? Change the future?
俺が 未来を…
That's...
そんなこと…
（岡部･紅莉栖）ハッ！
Kyouma,
I want...
...you to be the messiah.
～